healthychildren.org 2002-06-04

# HealthyMe.md - Today's Link for a Healthier You - --

## PRIVACY STATEMENT

HealthyMe.md, Inc. 

This privacy statement discloses the privacy practices for HealthyMe.md.

## Information Collection and Use

HealthyMe.md, Inc., is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. HealthyMe.md, Inc., collects information from our users at several different points on our Web site.

### Registration

In order to use this Web site, a user must first complete the registration form. During registration a user is required to give contact information (such as name and e-mail address). This information is used to contact the user about the services on our site for which the user has expressed interest. It is optional for the user to provide demographic information (such as income level and gender), and unique identifiers (such as social security number), but encouraged so we can provide a more personalized experience on our site. 

### Order

We request information from the user on our order form. Here a user must provide contact information (like name and shipping address) and financial information (like credit card number, expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes and to fill customers orders. If we have trouble processing an order, this contact information is used to get in touch with the user.

### Cookies

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the users hard drive containing information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. Once the user closes their browser, the cookie simply terminates. For instance, by setting a cookie on our site, the user would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. If a user rejects the cookie, the user may still use our site. The only drawback to this is that the user will be limited in some areas of our site. For example, the user will not be able to participate in any of our sweepstakes, contests or monthly drawings that take place. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site.

Some of our business partners use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies.

## Log Files

We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track users movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.

## Sharing

We will share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person.

We use an outside shipping company to ship orders, and a credit card processing company to bill users for goods and services. These companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes.

We partner with another party to provide specific services. When the user signs up for these services, we will share names, or other contact information that is necessary for the third party to provide these services. These parties are not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing these services.

## Links

This Web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.

### Newsletter

If a user wishes to subscribe to our newsletter, we ask for contact information such as name and e-mail address. 

### Surveys and Contests

From time-to-time our site requests information from users via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code, age level). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site.

### Tell-A-Friend

If a user elects to use our referral service for informing a friend about our site, we ask them for the friends name and e-mail address. HealthyMe.md will automatically send the friend a one-time e-mail inviting them to visit the site. You will receive a copy of that e-mail message. HealthyMe.md stores this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time e-mail. The friend may contact HealthyMe.md to request the removal of this information from the database.

### Security

This Web site takes every precaution to protect our users information. When users submit sensitive information via the Web site, your information is protected both online and off-line.

When our registration/order form asks users to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number and/or social security number), that information is encrypted and is protected with the best encryption software in the industry - SSL. While on a secure page, such as our order form, the lock icon on the bottom of Web browsers such as Netscape Navigator and Microsoft Internet Explorer become locked, as opposed to un-locked, or open, when you are just surfing.

While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also do everything in our power to protect user information off-line. All of our users information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, our billing clerk or a customer service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information. Our employees must use password-protected screen-savers when they leave their desk. When they return, they must re-enter their password to re-gain access to your information. Furthermore, ALL employees are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices. Every quarter, as well as any time new policies are added, our employees are notified and/or reminded about the importance we place on privacy, and what they can do to ensure our customers information is protected. Finally, the servers that we store personally identifiable information on are kept in a secure environment, behind a locked cage.

If you have any questions about the security at our Web site, you can send an e-mail to HealthyMe.md by using the Contact Us section of our Web site.

### Supplementation of Information

In order for this Web site to properly fulfill its obligation to our customers, it is necessary for us to supplement the information we receive with information from third party sources.

For example, to determine if our customers qualify for one of our credit cards, we use their name and social security number to request a credit report. Once we determine a users credit-worthiness, this document is destroyed. 

(or)

In order for this Web site to enhance its ability to tailor the site to an individuals preference, we combine information about the purchasing habits of users with similar information from our partners, Company Y & Company Z, to create a personalized user profile. When a user makes a purchase from either of these two companies, the companies collect and share that purchase information with us so we can tailor the site to our users preferences.

**Special Offers**

We send all new members a welcoming e-mail to verify password and username. Established members will occasionally receive information on products, services, special deals, and a newsletter. Out of respect for the privacy of our users we present the option to not receive these types of communications. Please see our choice and opt-out below.

**Site and Service Updates**

We also send the user site and service announcement updates. Members are not able to un-subscribe from service announcements, which contain important information about the service. We communicate with the user to provide requested services and in regards to issues relating to their account via email or phone.

**Correction/Updating Personal Information:**

If a users personally identifiable information changes (such as zip code), or if a user no longer desires our service, we will endeavor to provide a way to correct, update or remove that users personal data provided to us. This can usually be done at the member information page **** or by e-mailing our Customer Support **.** [Some sites may also provide telephone or postal mail options for updating **** or correcting **** personal information].

### Choice/Opt-out

Our users are given the opportunity to "opt-out" of having their information used for purposes not directly related to our site at the point where we ask for the information. For example, our order form has an opt-out mechanism so users who buy a product from us, but do not want any marketing material, can keep their e-mail address off of our lists. 

Users who no longer wish to receive our newsletter or promotional materials from our partners may opt-out of receiving these communications by replying to "unsubscribe" in the subject line in the e-mail or e-mail us HealthyMe.md using the contact us form found on our Web site.

Users of our site are always notified when their information is being collected by any outside parties. We do this so our users can make an informed choice as to whether they should proceed with services that require an outside party, or not.

### Notification of Changes

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our home page so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by way of an e-mail. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.
